[{
    "question": "Who is the shortest player to play in the NBA?",
    "choice1": "Earl Boykins",
    "choice2": "Nate Robinson",
    "choice3": "Spud Webb",
    "choice4": "Mussy Bogues",
    "answer": 4
}, {
    "question": "What team played in the most overall NBA Final series?",
    "choice1": "Celtics",
    "choice2": "Lakers",
    "choice3": "Bulls",
    "choice4": "Magic",
    "answer": 2
}, {
    "question": "Who won the Rookie of the Year Award in 2009?",
    "choice1": "Kevin Durant",
    "choice2": "Stephen Curry",
    "choice3": "Derrick Rose",
    "choice4": "Mitch Richmond",
    "answer": 1
}, {
    "question": "Who won the MVP in the 2008-2009 season?",
    "choice1": "Dwight Howard",
    "choice2": "Kobe Bryant",
    "choice3": "Lebron James",
    "choice4": "Dwayne Wade",
    "answer": 3
}, {
    "question": "Who won the 3-point contest three straight times?",
    "choice1": "Glen Rice",
    "choice2": "Voshon Lenard",
    "choice3": "Larry Bird",
    "choice4": "Predrag Stojakovic",
    "answer": 3
}, {
    "question": "Who has the nickname 'Hibachi'?",
    "choice1": "Wade",
    "choice2": "Howard",
    "choice3": "Arenas",
    "choice4": "Lebron",
    "answer": 3
}, {
    "question": "What number is Kobe Bryant?",
    "choice1": "24",
    "choice2": "23",
    "choice3": "8",
    "choice4": "4",
    "answer": 1
}, {
    "question": "Which basketball player starred in Space Jam?",
    "choice1": "Michael Jordan",
    "choice2": "Shaqueille O'Neil",
    "choice3": "Jeremey Lin",
    "choice4": "Lebron James",
    "answer": 1
}, {
    "question": "Why are the Los Angeles Lakers called the Lakers?",
    "choice1": "Their first arena was on a lake",
    "choice2": "Their founder was named 'Lake'",
    "choice3": "They originally came from the Minnesota",
    "choice4": "One of their legends names 'Lake'",
    "answer": 3
}, {
    "question": "What is depicted on the logo of the Golden State Warriors?",
    "choice1": "A basketball",
    "choice2": "A bear",
    "choice3": "A spearhead",
    "choice4": "A bridge",
    "answer": 4
}, {
    "question": "Who was the shortest player to win an MVP?",
    "choice1": "Allen Iverson",
    "choice2": "Steve Nash",
    "choice3": "Spud Webb",
    "choice4": "Charles Barkley",
    "answer": 1
}, {
    "question": "What is the record for the highest scoring average in a single-season?",
    "choice1": "35.4ppg",
    "choice2": "50.4ppg",
    "choice3": "42.8ppg",
    "choice4": "38.4ppg",
    "answer": 2
}, {
    "question": "What country is Manu Gin√≥bili from?",
    "choice1": "France",
    "choice2": "Argentina",
    "choice3": "Italy",
    "choice4": "United States",
    "answer": 2
}]